你知道他睡着后的恐惧吗
他的每条神经都战栗着
因为他脚下的土地崩塌
梦境在此展开
弗里德里希·尼采
欢迎收看八点档 贱人
《猛鬼街6：终极噩梦》
(春木市)
(俄亥俄州春木市 十年后)
(神秘的谋杀与自杀彻底摧毁了)
(镇上所有的儿童与青少年)
(存活的成年人出现集体精神病症)
(新证据显示有一名青少年幸存)
晚安 各位先生 各位女士 我是机长
Uh, good evening, ladies and gentlemen. This is your pilot.
系上安全带的指示灯已经亮起
Uh, you'll notice the "fasten seatbelt" sign is on.
我们正经过乱流
We're passing through a bit of turbulence here.
很不幸 我们无法飞高或飞低
Unfortunately, we can't get up over it and, uh, we can't get underneath it.
所以请忍耐 我们会尽快通过
Just hang in there. We'll get through this as soon as we can.
不好意思 小姐
Excuse me, miss.
- 什么事 - 我能换位子吗
- Yes? - Can I have a different seat, please?
今晚机位全满 先生 你恐怕得坐在原位
No, I'm afraid we're full tonight, sir. You're gonna have to stay put.
还是谢谢你
Thanks, anyway.
他会逼你帮助他
He's going to make you help him...
因为你是最后一个
...because you're the last.
听着
Listen...
我真的一定得换座位
...I really need to change this seat.
抱歉 我爱莫能助
I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do.
我有惧高症
I'm afraid of heights.
别这么胆小
Don't be a pussy.
哇啊
Whoa!
不公平 我差一点就逃出去了
It's not fair! I was almost out!
靠
Shit.
我会逮到你的 甜心 还有你的灵魂
I'll get you, my pretty, and your little soul too.
(榆树街1427号)
(出售 春木房仲)
天啊
God.
哇啊
Whoa!
天啊
Oh, God.
(售票亭)
一张
One ticket...
来回票
...round trip.
快一点 小子
Hurry up, boy.
你不能错过这班巴士
You don't wanna miss the bus.
巴士在开动的时候不能尖叫
Oh. No screaming while the bus is in motion.
惨了
Goddamn it.
(欢迎来到春木市)
现在当只小乖狗去捡吧
Now be a good little doggie and go fetch.
(提神药)
(克鲁格太太依旧下落不明)
(青少年收容所)
(仅限员工出入)
史宾瑟 我要确定你了解整个情况
Spencer, I wanna make sure that you understand our situation.
一个星期后你说会离开这里
In one week, you walk out of here.
我希望你回家之后行为有所改善
And I expect to see some changes in your behavior when you get home.
我知道你听得很清楚 我带你来这里因为我别无选择
I know you're hearing me. I put you in here because you gave me no choice.
- 下次我就永远把你丢在这里 - 谢谢你来看我 爸爸
- Next time, I'll leave you here and walk away. - Thanks for the visit, Dad.
你真会调教我儿子 原本我以为他会改善
Nice job on my kid. I expected to see some improvement.
他不是一辆车
He isn't a Toyota.
真是个王八蛋
What a jerk.
- 你还好吗 - 还好
- You okay? - Yeah.
爸爸来告诉我回家之后要遵守哪些规定
Dad came by to lay down some ground rules for when I come home.
不能再逃跑或放火烧他的车
No more running away, no more setting his cars on fire.
除了炸掉车库以外还有别的方式能引人注意
There are ways to get attention besides blowing up the garage.
他连眼睛都没眨一下
Yeah, he barely even blinked.
他只希望我长大后能变成他
All he wants me to do now is grow up to be him.
成为他的翻版
An exact copy.
我不想玩美式足球或和女同学约会时强暴她
I don't feel like playing football and date-raping coeds.
你迟早得面对你的父亲
One of these days, you'll have to face your father.
玛姬
Maggie.
瞧瞧我在史宾瑟房间找到什么
Look what I found in Spencer's room.
钢管炸弹是吗
A pipe bomb, huh?
那个啊 我是在向其他人示范一些生存技巧
Uh, that? Well, I was just showing the kids some survival techniques.
我整星期都忙着没收这些玩意儿
I've been confiscating stuff like this all week.
这些从哪里来的
Where do they get it?
把这个和其他武器一起放到楼下
Put this downstairs with the rest of the arsenal.
- 警方应该销毁这些东西 - 警方应该做很多事
- The police were to dispose of it. - Police are supposed to do a lot of things.
别跑 给我回来
Stop. Come back here.
- 别碰我 - 崔西
- Take your hands off me! - Tracy.
- 等等 出了什么问题 - 她殴打另外一个小孩
- What's the problem? - She was beating on one of the kids.
- 他想吃我豆腐 - 她不喜欢别人碰她
- He was trying to hit on me. - She doesn't like to be touched.
你今天要上我的课 对不对
We have a session today, yes?
我得上医生的课
I have Doc's class.
你去和他协调
Work around him.
对不起 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
你看过这只毒虫吗
You seen this junkie before?
没有 他是新面孔
No, he's new.
这可好了 今天下午又要去少年监狱填表格
Beautiful. Another afternoon shot doing juvie paperwork.
别这么麻烦了
Screw that shit.
直接带他去收容所吧
Let's just scoop him up and take him to the shelter.
让那些好心人应付他
Let the bleeding hearts do the typing.
很好 崔西
That's it. Come on, Tracy.
这样此对了 她真猛
That's it. Oh, yeah, she's bad.
群众都超爱她
The crowd Ioves her.
她准备赢得重量级拳击比赛的世界冠军
She's getting ready for the heavyweight champion boxing match of the world.
瞧瞧她出拳真猛 你流汗的时候真性感
Hey, hey, hey, look at her go. You know, you are sexy when you sweat.
你休想占我便宜 卡洛斯
You ain't getting none, Carlos. You ain't getting none.
- 你不会打一个残障人士吧 - 这样就叫残障
- You wouldn't hit a guy with a handicap. - You call it a handicap?
我认为你是娘炮 来单挑吧
I call it chicken, man. Come on, let's spar.
- 快点 放马过来 - 别闹了 崔西
- Come on, you yellow-bellied... Come on. - Forget it, Trace. I'm...
别退缩 你为何不回嘴
Don't tune out. Why don't you talk back to her?
就像你跟你老爸顶嘴吗 告诉你 史宾瑟
Like you talk back to your father? Let me tell you something, Spence.
我发现回嘴有害健康 我就闭上嘴 你懂吗
I stopped talking back when it became hazardous to my health. You know?
- 都准备好了吗 - 没问题
- So are we set? - Yeah, no problem.
我已经把钱给司机 只要在黎明前完成我们就自由了
I gave the driver our cash. As long as we do it before dawn, we're free.
这表示我们下礼拜就能去加州吃香喝辣
All right, that means we're gonna be living large in Cali before the week is out.
你最好十拿九稳 老兄
You better be sure, man.
相信我 我都安排好了 我比你更想离开这里
Trust me. I got all the bases covered. I need to get out of here more than you do.
你无法了解我多想离开这里
You don't know shit about needing to get out.
你生来家财万贯 富家子弟
Your family's a picnic, rich boy.
你认为我是自愿和你们这些白痴厮混吗
You think I hang around with you morons by choice?
至少你爸爸没设计你和他女朋友的姊姊上床
Your father didn't try to set you up with his girlfriend's older sister.
别提到我爸爸
Don't talk to me about fathers.
他也来探望你了吗
Yours come to visit too?
对 每次我闭上眼睛的时候
Yeah, every time I close my eyes.
好 这样可以
All right, that did it. Yep. Okay.
你最喜爱的学生又被逮到殴打其他小孩
They caught one of your star pupils beating up on one of our kids again.
- 崔西 - 我以为你说她有进步
- Tracy? - You said you were making progress.
我每星期只教这些孩子23分钟
I only get 23 minutes a week with these kids.
时间这么少 她没宰了他就算万幸
With that kind of attention, we're lucky she didn't kill him.
身为治疗师 你的态度真积极
Ha, ha. Oh, that's a good attitude for a therapist.
你知道吗 崔西脑海中埋藏着深沉的创伤
You know, Tracy's got some deep trauma buried inside of her head.
传统治疗不会奏效
Conventional therapy is not going to work.
梦境治疗就有效吗 你真是个嬉皮
And dream therapy is, huh? You're such a hippie.
我能经由梦境直达这些孩子们的内心
You know, I can reach these kids through their dreams.
给我一个机会 我就能解决你的小问题
Give me a chance, I can help with your little problem.
我没有小问题
I don't have a little problem.
我只是不断做同样的梦 而且我能应付
I just have a little reoccurring dream and I'm handling it fine.
你不是领钱来解梦的
And you are not being paid to be a dream doctor.
我几乎没领薪水 所以我得做我认为正确的事
I'm barely being paid. That's why I gotta do what I think is right.
- 这是新的吗 - 你喜欢吗
- This is new. - You like it?
这些是远古的梦境恶魔
These are ancient dream demons.
据说他们在活人的梦境里游走
Supposedly, they roam the dreams of the living...
直到找到最邪恶变态的人类
...till they find the most evil, twisted human imaginable.
然后他们就给此人越界的力量
Then they give him the power to cross the line...
将我们的噩梦化为现实
...and turn our nightmares into reality.
玛姬 警方又带来一个年轻人
Maggie, cops just brought in another kid.
他的状况很糟 好几天没睡 严重失忆
Real mess. Hasn't slept for days, bad case of amnesia.
他们需要你立即评估
They need your evaluation right away.
- 你多久没睡了 - 久到我记不得
- How long have you been awake? - As far as I can remember.
不知道 大约三天
I don't know. About three days.
看起来像是三个礼拜
Looks more like three weeks.
对 这就是失忆症的美妙之处
Yeah, well, that's the wonder of amnesia.
让你永远搞不清楚状况
Just always keeps you guessing.
你从哪里来的
Where are you from?
我不知道
I don't know!
我只知道无论我来自哪里 都是最后一个
All I know is that wherever I'm from, I was the last.
- 最后一个什么 - 生还者
- The last what? - Survivor.
听着 你有咖啡因药丸或咖啡吗 或是可乐
Look, do you have any, um, caffeine pills or coffee, maybe some Coke?
我是指汽水
I meant the soda.
坐下
Sit down.
- 你为何要醒着 - 因为如果我睡着
- Why do you wanna stay awake? - Because if I fall asleep...
就再也醒不来
... I'm not waking up.
- 你为何这样想 - 这不是我的想法
- Why do you think that? - I don't think it.
而是一种感觉
I feel it.
如果我睡着 说会有麻烦
If I fall asleep, there's gonna be trouble.
(克鲁格太太依旧下落不明)
春木市
"Springwood."
水塔
Water tower.
墙上有4567瓶啤酒
Four thousand, five hundred.
墙上有67瓶啤酒
And sixty-seven bottles of beer on the wall.
墙上有4567瓶啤酒
Four thousand, five hundred sixty-seven bottles of beer.
若其中一瓶啤酒掉下来
If one of those bottles should happen to fall.
就会
What a case of...
若你再不闭嘴 我就用酒瓶砸爆你的头
Hell, I'll break a bottle over your head if you don't shut the fuck up!
墙上有4567瓶啤酒
Four thousand, five hundred and sixty-six bottles of beer on the wall.
我不会说出去
I won't tell.
你来了 记得应该怎么做
Now you're it. Remember what you have to do.
你要擒抱我
You gotta tag me.
乖女孩
That's a girl.
在这里 过来
Over here. Come on.
来爸爸这里
Come to Daddy.
和我玩
Play with me.
告诉我我是谁
Tell me who I am.
我不会说出去
I won't tell.
放我走 白痴 我是你的记忆
Free me, you idiot! I'm your fucking memory!
糟糕
Oh, shit.
王八蛋
Asshole.
你梦到什么
What were you dreaming about?
一个房间
A room.
一栋房子
A house.
一个小女孩
A little girl.
和那篇报导里的小镇
Something about, uh, the town from my article.
我记得有一座水塔
I remember a water tower.
你记得那篇报导从哪里来的吗
The article, do you remember where you got it?
- 不记得 - 那个小女孩长什么模样
- No. - The little girl, what did she look like?
- 棕发和红色缎带 - 红色缎带
- Brown hair with red ribbons. - Red ribbons.
情况不妙 你和他的梦境有关联
I don't like it. There's some connection between your dreams and his dreams...
而他的梦境是噩耗
...and his dreams mean bad news.
我知道你认为我疯了 但我能感觉到
You think I'm crazy, but I can feel it.
这里为何没人能谈一些梦境以外的事情
Why can't anybody talk about anything but dreams around here?
- 我受不了这些胡说八道 - 你不相信
- I'm sick of hearing about this bullshit. - You don't believe that.
你认为你能解开这个男孩的谜题 进一步帮助自己
You think you can solve this puzzle, it can help with yours.
我没有谜题
I don't have a puzzle.
你有 虽然你自认无所不知
Yes, you do. And although you think you know everything...
你或许还没准备好面对这男孩要让你看见的一切
...you may not be ready to face what this boy is gonna show you.
- 我没说过想回去 - 我治疗过失忆症息者
- I never said I wanted to go back there. - I've dealt with amnesiacs before.
带你回春木市会引发一些你记忆中的片段
Taking you to Springwood is gonna trigger some spark to help you remember.
我不需要回忆说知道 那是一个烂地方
I don't need a spark to help me to remember that it was a bad place.
要去你自己去 我要留在这里快乐地继续失忆
You want a spark, you go. I'll stay here, sparkless but happy.
我和你一起去 别担心
I'll be right there with you. Don't worry.
凯利 我要借用一下厢型车
Kelly, gonna take the van for a little while.
(爬虫类青少年龌龊收容所)
(春木市 两英里)
(欢迎来到春木市 人口 15265 居住的好地方)
我叫你别让我睡着 这个要求很过分吗
I told you not to let me fall asleep. Is that too much to ask for?
- 回去 - 天啊 靠边停
- Go back. - Oh, my God. Pull over.
孩子 孩子 醒醒
John. John, wake up.
- 糟糕 - 这可好了
- Shit. - Oh, great.
真高兴和你在这里见面
Funny meeting you here.
你的开车技术真棒
Well, nice driving.
你们在这里搞什么
What the hell are you guys doing here?
真棒的计划 混蛋
Great plan, asshole.
- 差点就成功了 - 我真不敢相信
- lt almost worked. - I can't believe you people.
你们竟然耍这种花样
Pulling a stunt like that.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我们得先找到电话
Look, the first thing we have to do is find a telephone.
然后你们打给凯利 告诉他你们在哪里 懂吗
You call Kelly and tell him where you are, understand?
接着我再想办法送你们回家
And then we have to figure out how to get you home.
你们有在听吗
Are you listening?
别对我吼
Don't scream at me.
- 是你的驾驶技术差点害死我们 - 对
- lt was your driving that almost killed us. - Yeah.
(春木镇市集今天登场)
(春木镇市集)
(成人75分钱 儿童十分钱)
两个一块钱 快来这里
Two. Two for a dollar, right here.
来吧 两个只要一块钱
Get them here. Here you go. Two for a dollar.
好 你们先找电话打给凯利和他说你们没事
All right. First I want you to find a phone, call Kelly and tell him you're all right.
然后我要你们回车上直接开回收容所
I want you to get in that van and drive straight back to the shelter.
你们办得到吗 还是我得报警
Think you can handle that, or do I have to call the police?
- 别碰他们 - 你滚开
- Get away from them. - You go away.
- "还是我得报警" - 走开
- "Or do I have to call the police?" - Go away. Go away.
- 她又不是我妈 - 她脱掉胸罩了
- She ain't my mother. - There goes the bra.
谁要吃蜜桃馅饼 味道还不错
Who wants some peach cobbler here? It's not burned too bad.
直接从中间切开即可
You can just cut it right in the middle there.
就是这里 就是这里
Step right up here. Right here. Here's the place.
来这里准没错
This is the place you wanna be here.
- 没有小孩 - 什么
- There are no kids. - What?
市集居然没有小孩
A town fair and there are no kids.
你们小心点
Guys, look out.
你们在那里做什么
Guys, what the heck you doing over there?
- 怎么了 史宾瑟 - 电话故障
- What's up, Spence? - This phone's out of order.
- 这座小镇也不对劲 - 一点都没错
- So is this town. - You are not kidding.
真是漂亮又讨人喜欢的小孩子 你们愿意来和我们住吗
Oh, what beautiful, adorable children. Would you like to come and live with us?
我们家里很久没有小孩了
It's been so long since we've had children in the house.
好久了
So long.
我保证这次会不一样
This time, I swear it'll be different.
这次我会把你们小心藏好 他就永远找不到你们
This time, I'll be careful and I'll hide you better so that he'll never find you.
你看 我抓到你的鼻子了
Lookie, I got your nose. Lookie.
艾瑟
Ethel.
我要我的孩子回来
I want my children back.
你知道他们会把他带来
You know they bring him.
瞧瞧你们干的好事
Now, see what you done did?
老天爷
Jesus.
- 我们好像在演《双峰》 - 没错
- We're in Twin Peaks here. - Definitely.
- 我们热闹看够了吗 - 够了
- Have we seen enough? - Yeah.
很好
Good.
好 回车上吧
All right. Come on, back in the van.
- 这是个非常好的主意 - 立刻上车 快点
- You know, that's a very good idea. - Now. Go!
希望他们能顺利回去
I hope they make it.
去听听学校的人有何说法
Let's see what they can tell us at the school.
- 什么 - 某人敲响那些钟
- What? - Somebody rang those bells.
我们真幸运
Lucky us.
崔西 后面有一张地图
Trace, there's a map back here.
我有说我需要地图吗
Did I say I needed a map?
我忘不了那些人看我们的眼神
I can't get over the way those people were looking at us.
对 真诡异
Yeah, that was weird.
糟糕
TRACY. Shit.
你真有一套
Nice going.
天才才会沿着原路绕圈圈
It takes talent to travel in a complete circle.
而且你让我头晕
And you're making me dizzy.
天啊
Jeez.
你非抽不可吗
Do you have to do that?
你真是只毒虫 你知道吗
You're such a heigh-ho, you know that?
我不抽这玩意儿 我需要保持感官敏锐
I don't play that shit. I need all the senses I got.
把这玩意儿熄灭 你每十秒钟就抽一根
Put that fucking thing out. It's hard enough staying awake...
- 让人很难保持清醒 - 这能让我放松
- ...without you lighting up every 10 seconds. - This relaxes me.
我能用这两根手指让你放松 我直接戳死你
I can relax you with these two fingers. I'll just puncture your heart.
还会把座椅弄脏
Mess up these seats.
你需要打一炮
You need to get laid.
现在你需要地图了吗
Would you like the map now?
- 不 我不需要任何地图 - 好
- No, I don't need any map. - Okay.
你当然不需要
No, of course not.
- 你为何停下来 - 你看
- Why'd you stop? - Look.
这可好了
Oh, great.
地图给我
Give me the map.
少罗嗦
Not a word.
卡洛斯 我说我要看地图
Carlos, I asked you for the map.
这是怎么回事
What is this? Hey.
卡洛斯 我说我要看地图
Carlos. I asked you for the map.
什么
What?
地图写说我们完蛋了
Yeah, well, the map says we're fucked.
好 你有过两次机会 现在轮到我
Okay, look, you've had two chances. Now it's my turn.
- 呆头鹅 - 很好
- Dickhead. - Nice.
(春木高中)
你们全都要通过笔试和口试
You will all be expected to pass both a written and an oral examination.
别打扰他
Don't disturb him.
你们需要读这些
You will need to study this.
日期必须正确 如果排错我们会搞不清楚
We've got to get the dates right. If they get out of order, we get very confused.
(布鲁克·叶顿 七岁)
(失踪人口 芭比·葛拉斯 八岁)
(搜寻克鲁格 七岁男童失踪)
(春木市发现另一具肢解尸体)
(克鲁格之女)
孩子
John.
- 你来过这里 - 什么
- You were here. - What?
欢迎
Welcome...
来到佛莱迪入门班
...to Freddy 101.
1493年 佛莱迪远渡重洋
Fourteen hundred and ninety-three Freddy sailed across the sea
这些日期都在十年之内 这里发生什么事
These dates, they're all within a 10-year period. What the hell happened here?
佛莱迪来到这里
Freddy happened here.
这是关键
Here's a crucial point.
谁知道我在说什么吗
Anybody know what I'm getting at?
谁知道 大家别这样
Anybody? Come on, people.
我们上次才说过 他们此是在这时带走他的小孩
We covered this. This is where they took away his child.
哪个小孩
What child?
把他带走 带去镇上的孤儿院
Taken away, put in the town orphanage.
佛莱迪有一个小孩
Freddy had a kid.
1494年
Fourteen hundred and ninety-four
佛莱迪回来想要更多
Freddy came back to look for more
- 我们没办法离开 - 因为是你在开车
- There's no way out. - Not with you driving.
- 你也没好到哪儿去 - 至少我只花了一半的时间
- Yeah, well, you didn't do much better. - No, but at least I did it in half the time.
- 你要去哪里 - 离开
- Come on, where are you going? - Away.
我们累到搞不清楚方向 去找玛姬吧
We're too fried to see straight. Let's just find Maggie.
我才不需要成年人监督
'm not turning myself over for any adult supervision.
我要休息一下
This girl's getting some rest.
其实我看见适合我的社区空无一人
In fact, I think I see my kind of neighborhood up ahead: empty.
她发疯了
You know, she's losing it.
- 可悲的是我开始喜欢她 - 的确很可悲
- The sad thing is I'm starting to like her. - That is sad.
崔西 等一下
Come on, Trace, wait up.
(榆树街)
就是这栋房子 完全属于我们
This is the one. We'll have it all to ourselves.
- 但是没有暖气 - 也没有水电 对不对
- Bet there's no heat. - No plumbing, right?
你们死不了的
You'll survive.
(出售 春木房仲)
来吧
Come on.
- 你要去哪里 - 去楼上找一张床
- Where you going? - Gonna go upstairs and find a bed.
我累死了
Man, I'm tired.
我要找厕所
I gotta find a bathroom.
天啊 这里让收容所变得像五星级饭店
Jeez, this place makes the shelter look like The Ritz.
太好了
Great. Well...
这总比睡在街上好 对不对 卡洛斯
...at least it beats the streets, right, Carlos?
太舒服了
Oh, this is good.
我要先睡一觉
I'm gonna get some sleep...
早上我就载大家回家 没错
...and I will get us out of here in the morning. That's right.
天啊
Jeez.
你觉得那小子为何说不能睡着
Why do you think that kid said not to fall asleep?
因为他是个怪胎
Because he's a lame-o freak.
玛姬小姐最爱的神经病
Miss Maggie's pet psycho.
卡洛斯 卡洛斯
Carlos! Carlos!
卡洛斯
Carlos!
崔西
Tracy?
- 卡洛斯 - 崔西
- Carlos! - Tracy?
- Carlos? - Tracy?
你跑到哪里去 你为何不听我的话 卡洛斯
Where the hell are you? Why aren't you listening to me, Carlos?
- 该死 门又卡住了 - 我不要再给你酒
- Damn, the door's sticking again. - No, I ain't giving you a damn bottle.
- 准备好了吗 - 我要全部倒出来
- Is it ready? - I'm gonna pour it all out.
崔西
Tracy?
Tracy? Ugh!
崔西 你在哪里
Tracy, where are you?
在你后面
Behind you.
妈妈
Mama?
Mama.
你的听力或许不太好
Maybe you don't hear so good.
我应该替你清清耳朵
Maybe I clean out your ears for you.
不 妈妈 拜托你 我一直都很乖
No, no, Mama, please. I've been a good boy. You don...
你不了解 我一直都很乖
You don't understand. I've been good, Mama.
求求你别让我变成聋子 妈妈
Please, don't make me deaf, Mama. Please.
- 我很抱歉 - 我不抱歉
- I'm sorry. - I'm not.
卡洛斯 把耳朵借给我
Oh, Carlos, lend me your ear.
不要
No!
助听器还给我
Give me my hearing back!
好棒
Yes.
在哪里
Where is it?
不
No. No.
你不会这样做吧 老兄
You wouldn't do that, would you, man?
不要 求求你
No, no, no. Please. No, man.
不要
No, no, no.
不要 求求你 不要
No, no. No, please. No, no.
不要
No.
不要 不要 不要
No. No, no, no. No.
很高兴听见你的消息 卡洛斯
Nice hearing from you, Carlos. Ha, ha.
卡洛斯
Carlos?
Carlos.
我找不到卡洛斯
I can't find Carlos.
你看见电视上的东西了吗
You see what's on this TV?
我要开车去找他
I gotta take the van. I'm gonna look for him.
让开
Give me some room.
史宾瑟
Spence! Spencer!
不要睡着 快点离开
Don't fall asleep, man! Get out!
史宾瑟 快点离开
Spencer, get out, man!
卡洛斯
Carlos, man.
我们正在找你
We were just looking for you.
史宾瑟 史宾瑟 不要睡着
Spence! Spencer! Don't fall asleep, man!
史宾瑟 你这个蠢毒虫
Spencer, you stupid stoner!
(春木市孤儿院)
我们不应该来这里
We shouldn't even be here.
我们应该是来调查你的背景 不是死掉杀人狂的小孩
We're supposed to be finding out about you, not some dead killer's kid.
两者可能是同一件事
We might be talking about the same thing.
整座小镇的人开口闭口都是克鲁格
Look, the whole town is obsessing on this Krueger character.
你别再提他
Don't you start.
但他们为何要怕我
But why else would they be afraid of me?
为何我还活着 其他人全都死光
Why else am I still alive when everybody else is dead?
跳吧 跳吧 跳跃的灵魂
Skip, skip, skip to my Lou.
跳跃的灵魂 亲爱的
Skip to my Lou, my darlin'.
跳吧 跳吧 跳跃的灵魂
Skip, skip, skip to my Lou.
跳跃的灵魂 亲爱的
Skip to my Lou, my darlin'.
玛莎 不要跑 大家手牵手
Martha, no running. Everyone, hold hands.
跳吧 跳吧 跳跃的灵魂
Skip, skip, skip to my Lou.
你们回来了 真好
Oh, you've come back. How nice.
你还记得我吗
Do you remember me?
当然记得 小男孩 每个小孩我都记得很清楚
Well, of course, I do, my boy. I remember every one of my children.
特别是你
Especially you.
当时你是个漂亮的小女孩
What a pretty little girl you were.
我记得你和你
And I remember you and you.
- 你记得克鲁格的孩子吗 - 当然
- Do you remember the Krueger child? - Ha, ha. Of course.
是谁
Who was it?
我们不能揭露孩子的真实身分
We're not permitted to disclose a child's real identity.
玛莉莎 你要把球让给芭比玩
Oh, Melissa. Melissa. You must let Bobby have the ball.
- 孩子 - 过来 没关系的
- John. - Come here. Come on.
大家一起玩
That's all right. You share.
不知道谁光着脚丫子 让我看看
I wonder who has a little bare footie around here. Let me see.
克鲁格 可能是凯文或凯尔
K. Krueger? Could mean anything from Kevin to Kyle.
意思只是这里有一个叫这个名字的小孩
All it really means is there was a child here by that name.
不对
No.
是我
It's me. Ha, ha.
没错
Yes. Oh, look....
我是他的孩子
I'm his kid.
所以他让我活下来
That's why he's kept me alive.
他想和我玩变态的游戏
He's trying to play some sick game with me.
他死了 好吗 他死了 你不是他的孩子
He is dead, all right? He's dead and you're not his kid.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
她记得我
She remembered me.
她也记得我 和另外50个幻想出来的朋友
She remembered me too and 50 other imaginary friends.
我们离开这里吧
Let's get out of here.
我们来画画 今天一整天都还没画画
Let's draw a picture. We haven't drawn a picture all day.
很好 一笔一画 很好玩吧
There you go. Clippety-clop, clippety-clop. Isn't that fun?
- 玛姬 - 崔西
- Maggie. - Tracy.
- 我不敢相信能找到你 - 你为何还在这里
- I can't believe I found you. - What are you still doing here?
我找不到卡洛斯 史宾瑟在一栋旧房子里喝酒
I can't find Carlos and Spencer's wasted at this old house and...
我们得比佛莱迪早一步找到他们
We gotta get to them before Freddy does.
- 不 - 佛莱迪是谁
- No. - Who's Freddy?
- 路上再说 快点 - 好
- I'll tell you on the way. Come on! - Yeah. All right.
真该死
Goddamn it.
好 再说一次
All right, once again.
这是你的大脑
This is your brain.
这是你嗑药后的大脑
This is your brain on drugs.
有问题吗
Questions?
有 你嗑了什么药
Yeah. What are you on?
看起来只是一把平底锅和几颗鸡蛋
Looks like a frying pan and some eggs to me.
史宾瑟 咱们去神游吧
Hey, Spence, let's trip out.
好酷
Oh, cool.
- In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida 亲爱的 - 哇啊
- In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida, honey - Whoa!
你不知道我爱你吗
Don't you know that I love you.
In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida 宝贝
In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida, baby.
你不知道我永远是对的吗
Don't you know that I'll always be true.
他不见了
Now he's gone.
- 他想必睡着了 - 你们俩找这里和楼上
- He must've fallen asleep. - Look here and upstairs.
- 我去楼下找 - 他们已经不在这里了
- I'm gonna look downstairs. - They're not here anymore.
你行行好可以吗 去找就对了
Just humor me, will you, please? And look.
我在哪里
Where am I?
跳起来 男孩
Jump, boy.
哇啊
Whoa!
跳起来
Jump.
哇啊
Whoa!
- 爸爸 - 像我一样
- Dad? - Be like me.
像我一样
Be like me. Be like me.
听爸爸的话准没错
Father knows best.
别打了
Oh, stop.
我和你不一样 我也不想变成你
I'm not like you. I don't wanna be like you.
我不像你
I'm not like you.
像我一样
Be like me.
不 我要加强火力
Now I'm playing with power.
好的
All right.
超级史宾瑟 太棒了
Super Spencer. Yeah.
画面真漂亮
Hey, great graphics.
我来到这里了
Whoa, I'm here.
卡洛斯
Carlos?
好棒
Yeah.
我找到史宾瑟了
I found Spencer!
好 把他压住
Okay. Hold him down.
糟糕
Oh, shit.
- 等一下 - 老天爷
- Hold on. Hold on. - Jesus Christ. Hold on.
- 发生什么事 - 他被困在噩梦中
- What's happening? - He's stuck in a nightmare.
- 他被狠狠地殴打 - 赶快叫醒他
- It's kicking the shit out of him. - Well, wake him up.
- 他吸太多大麻了 - 史宾瑟 天啊
- He's too wasted. - Spencer. Jesus.
是佛莱迪
It's Freddy.
- 我们必须救他出来 - 压住他
- Get him out. - Hold him.
我要进入他的梦中 在他丧命之前救他出来
I'll go into his dream, try and bring him out before he gets killed.
- 快点按住他 - 这太疯狂了
- Come on. Hold him. - That's crazy.
这算什么 很理智吗
Well, what do you call that, rational?
左 右
Right, left. Right, left. Right, left.
- 他快被整死了 - 我必须进入梦里
- He's getting trashed. - I have to go in.
佛莱迪怎么办
What about Freddy?
佛莱迪不会伤害我 我是他的孩子
Freddy won't hurt me. I'm family.
好 你要怎么进去
Okay, so how are you gonna go in?
这
Well...
你必须打昏我
...you're gonna have to lay me out.
- 搞什么 - 他妈的快点打昏我
- What is... - Come on, just fucking lay me out!
等等 医生说要用不同的方式
Wait a second. Doc told me a different way.
别罗嗦 动手说对了
There's no time to talk. Just do it!
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
我说过有更容易的方式
I told you I knew an easier way.
医生总是说要专心冥想
"Concentration and meditation." That's what Doc always says.
这里太神奇了
This place is incredible.
- 喷溅 - 那是他吗
- Splat. - Is that him?
跳起来 男孩
Jump, boy.
糟糕 史宾瑟
Oh, shit. Spencer.
快点 孩子 放开我
Come on, John. Let go of me. Let go.
立刻离开这里 崔西
Get out of here. Now, Tracy. Now.
你忘了拿能量手套
Hey, you forgot the Power Glove.
不 王八蛋
No! Bastard!
像我一样 像我一样 像我一样
Be like me. Be like me. Be like me.
史宾瑟 不要
Spencer, do...
真想不到 我获得最高分
What do you know? I beat my high score.
好棒
Oh, yeah.
重新办正事的感觉太棒了
Great to be back in business.
这都得感谢你
Thanks to you.
爸爸一直在等你 小女孩
Daddy's waiting for you, little girl.
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut the fuck up, man.
崔西
Tracy.
史宾瑟死了 我无法阻止他
Spencer's gone. I couldn't stop it.
孩子还在里面
John's still in there.
我叫不醒他
I couldn't wake him up.
你振作一点 我们要怎么做
Come on, snap out of it! What are we gonna do?
我们要把他抬起来离开这里
We're gonna pick him up and we're gonna get the hell out of here.
别又来了
Not again.
我不会再落入他的陷阱
He's not gonna get me again.
无论如何我都不会离开这张床
Nothing is gonna make me get off this bed.
该死
Damn it.
我恨这栋房子
I hate this house.
(欢迎来到春木市 人口 15265)
(居住的好地方)
(出现紧急状况请拉绳子)
强尼
Johnny.
我在上面
Up here.
我知道你为何放我走
I know why you let me go.
你认为我是你老爸吗
Oh, do you think I'm your daddy?
错了
Wrong.
但你让我活下来
But you let me live.
直到你带我女儿回来为止
Only long enough for you to bring me back my daughter.
你女儿
Your daughter?
现在她要带我去一座新游乐场
And now she's gonna take me to a whole new playground.
不要
No!
准备降落
Grounded!
孩子
John!
天啊 玛姬 发生什么事
Oh, my God, Maggie. What's going on?
快点玛姬 我们走
Come on, Maggie. Let's go.
我们快点离开这里
Let's get out of here. Let's get the hell out of here.
不是男孩
It's...It's not a boy.
是
It's....
我们必须立刻离开这里
Come on. We gotta get out of here. Now. Come on.
快点玛姬 我们走
Come on, Maggie. Let's go.
我们必须立刻离开
Come on, let's go now!
你忘了你从哪里来的 孩子
You forgot where you came from, kid...
但我知道你要去哪里
...but I know where you're going. Ha, ha.
(欢迎来到春木市 人口数 7741)
我要去旅行了
It's traveling time.
玛姬
TRACY. Maggie.
怎么了 玛姬 快点上车
What's wro... Maggie, get in the van. Come on.
快点上车 我们要离开这里
Come on, get in the van! We gotta get the hell out of here!
天啊
Oh, God.
我们走
Let's go.
无论发生了什么事都不是你的错
Whatever happened, it wasn't your fault.
- 我甚至不在场 - 一定会再发生
- I wasn't even there, man. - It's gonna happen again.
卡洛斯 崔西和史宾瑟 躲在厢型车的后座
Carlos, Tracy, and Spencer stowed away in the back of the shelter van.
他们想逃走 你相信吗
They were trying to escape. Can you believe it?
我就叫他们去打电话 他们应该打给你的
So I took them to the phone. They were supposed to call you.
无名氏和我则去学校查看
John Doe and l were gonna check out the school.
但崔西和我们走散
But Tracy got separated.
- 然后他们说逃走了 - 你在说什么
- And then they ran away. - What the hell are you talking about?
我是说卡洛斯 史宾瑟 和那个无名氏
I'm talking about Carlos and Spencer and the John Doe.
凯利 他们就这样凭空消失
Kelly, they just disappeared.
你处理太多案件了 玛姬 那些孩子从未来过这里
You've been handling too many cases, Maggie. Those kids were never here.
若有新来的孩子我会记得
I would remember any new arrival.
凯利 48小时前 我带来一个无名氏
Kelly, I'm talking about 48 hours ago. I brought you a John Doe.
别告诉我你不记得 是你处理太多案件了
You don't remember? You're the one who's handling too many cases.
去休 急吧 玛姬
Get some rest, Maggie.
然后
And then, um...
我们回去 没人记得那孩子或卡洛斯
...we got back and no one remembers John or Carlos.
彷佛他们从未存在过
It's like they never existed.
我一直听见奇怪的话
I've been hearing strange shit.
好像某些人梦见卡洛斯
Like some of the kids are dreaming about Carlos.
他们却不记得他
And they don't even remember him.
我记得他
I remember him.
为什么
Why?
因为我能控制我的梦 我不会被你看见的东西所愚弄
Because I can control my dreams. I'm not fooled by this thing you saw.
- 佛莱迪 - 无论他是什么东西
- Freddy. - Whatever he is...
他在操控梦境与现实的界线
...he's fucking with the line between dreams and reality.
他不仅杀死卡洛斯和其他人
He didn't just kill Carlos and the others.
他还抹灭他们
He erased them.
不是男孩 不是男孩
It's not a boy. It's not a boy. It's not a boy.
妈妈
Mother!
Mother.
该死
Shit.
- 你准备好杀人了 - 我是要自卫
- You're getting ready to kill somebody. - Defend myself.
他要操控的是你的心智
It's your mind he'll go for.
和你的恐惧
Your fear.
我就知道
Oh, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
(领养判决书)
玛姬 你在干什么
Maggie? What are you doing?
他们是谁
Who are they?
- 给我 - 我一定要知道
- Let me have that. - I have to know.
我不知道他们是谁 他们不肯告诉我
I don't know. I don't know who they were. They wouldn't tell me.
他们规定彼此不能接触
They have rules about no contact.
但我们接触过了
Oh, there's been contact.
这样此对了
You're it. You're it.
来爸爸这边
Come to Daddy.
我不会说出去
I won't tell.
天啊
Oh, God.
佛莱迪 求求你
Fred, please.
我不会说出去
I won't tell.
我们需要谈一谈 萝莉塔
We need to talk, Loretta.
进屋去 亲爱的
Go inside, honey.
我不会说出去
Oh, I won't tell.
我叫你别乱碰我的东西
I told you never to go near my things.
我不是故意的 佛莱迪
Oh, I didn't mean to, Fred...
是这样吗
Right? Isn't that right?
对
Right.
住手
Stop.
凯瑟琳
Katherine.
你真是个小艺术家
You were such a little artist.
不可能
No, it can't be.
我知道我是谁
I know who I am.
你是我的亲骨肉
You're my blood.
只有你能带我出去 在你的脑海中
Only you could have brought me out, in your mind.
但你不可能是我爸爸
But you can't be my father.
他们把你从我身边带走 但我让他们付出代价
They took you away from me, but I made them pay.
我夺走他们所有的孩子
I took all their children away from them.
现在
And now...
一切都结束了
...that's over.
走吧
Come on.
收容所
The shelter.
该重来一次了
Time to start all over again.
但这里不是春木市
But this isn't Springwood.
每座城市都有一条榆树街
Every town has an Elm Street.
(榆树街)
崔西
Tracy.
准备好了吗
Is it ready?
崔西小乖
Tracy, girl.
爸爸回家了
Daddy's home.
爸爸 你死了
Daddy, you're dead.
我回家了 亲爱的
I'm home, darling.
来和我打声招呼
Come say hello.
我不要 爸爸
I don't want to, Daddy.
来吧 让爸爸爽一下
Come on. Give Daddy some honey.
没人会知道
No one has to know.
你不是我爸爸 你不是我爸爸
You're not my daddy. You're not my daddy!
别这样 崔西
Come on, Tracy.
去死吧
Here!
现在你爱我了吗
Do you love me now?!
Do you love me now?! Come on!
他死了
He's dead.
我爸爸死了
My daddy's dead.
他死了
He's dead.
He's dea...
不让爸爸爽一下吗
No honey for Daddy?
这年头的小孩是怎么回事
What's with kids today, huh?
不懂得尊重长辈
No respect.
你再也吓不了我
You can't scare me anymore.
你最好说大声一点
Oh, you better speak up.
想必是我的耳朵聋了
Oh, must be my deaf ear.
有哈本事尽管使出来 贱人
Kung fu this, bitch.
这是我的梦 我想怎样都行
This is my dream and I do what I want.
这或许是你的梦 但是规则由我订
It might be your dream, but it's my rules.
医生 我需要找医生
Doc. I need to talk to Doc.
- 好 - 快点
- Okay. - Come on!
(请勿奔跑)
崔西
Tracy?
- 医生 是你吗 - 对 崔西 你在哪里
- Doc. Doc, is that you? - Yeah, Tracy, where are you?
我在其中一个置物柜里 快点放我出去
I'm over here in one of the lockers. You gotta get me out.
- 你在哪里 - 我在这里
- Where the hell are you? - Right here.
你教她很多东西
You taught her a lot.
但她要学的还有很多
But there's so much more to learn.
这样如何 医生
How about this, Doc?
棍子和石头或许能让我骨折
Sticks and stones may break my bones...
但没有任何东西杀得了我
...but nothing will ever kill me.
让我想想看
Well, let's see now.
他们先想烧死我
First they tried burning me. Ha, Ha.
然后想埋葬我
Then they tried burying me.
但这是我的最爱
But this, this is my favorite.
他们甚至试过圣水
They even tried holy water.
但我此是死不了
But I just keep on ticking.
因为这是他们给我的承诺
Because they promised me that.
- 他们 - 梦境中的人
- They? - The dream people.
给我这份工作的那些人
The ones that gave me this job.
在梦境中
In dreams...
我永生不死
... I am forever.
可惜你没办法
Too bad you're not.
医生
Doc.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
我想出消灭他的办法了
I think I've got a way to get him.
你有什么计划 医生
So, what's the plan, Doc?
- 谢谢 - 你无法在梦中杀死他
- Thanks. - You can't get him in a dream.
但若这能出来 他就能出来
But if this can come out, he can come out.
若他能出来 说会流血
And if he can come out, he can bleed.
- 然后死去 - 对
- And die. - Right.
你怎么知道我何时逮到他
How will you know when I got him?
我会用监测器找到你然后带你出来
I'm gonna find you with this and then I'm bringing you out.
你必须紧抓着他 把他拖出来
Now, you've got to be holding him to carry him out.
我知道
I know.
他会试着欺骗你 就像他欺骗崔西一样
Now, he's gonna try and trick you like he tricked Tracy.
也会用你的双眼愚弄你 你要使用这些
And he's gonna try to use your eyes to fool you. You'll use these.
- 少来 - 你想活命吗
- Get the hell out of here. - You wanna live?
这些在这里毫无意义
These mean nothing here.
但在梦中你想怎样都行
But in the dream, they can be anything you want.
他进入你的脑中 你也进入他的
He got inside of your head, you get inside of his.
这是我的任务 对不对
That's my job, isn't it?
小心点 他很了解怎么做最能伤害你
Be careful. He's good at finding out what hurts the most.
- 没错 - 因此你得带我和你一起去
- Exactly. - That's why you gotta take me with you.
不行
I can't.
必须是我和他的对决
It's gotta be me and him.
好的 医生
All right, Doc.
让我进去吧
Put me in.
把她接上去
Strap her in.
好的
Okay.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
- 好 - 很好
- Okay. - Good.
十
Ten...
九
...nine...
八
...eight...
七 六
...seven, six...
五 四
...five, four...
三 二
...three, two...
一
...one.
(艾默森郡博物馆)
进入他的脑中
And get inside his brain.
我进入他的记忆里了
I'm in his memories.
一百个疯子的小孩
Son of a hundred maniacs Son of a hundred maniacs.
很好
Oh, yeah. Ha, ha.
佛莱迪
Freddy.
你好了没有 孩子
You ready for it, boy?
从我收容你的那天起 你就是个废物
You've been a waste since the day I took you in.
现在你该吃药了
Now it's time to take your medicine.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
可以再抽我一下吗
May I have another?
你想知道痛苦的秘密吗
You wanna know the secret of pain?
一旦停止感受 就能开始加以利用
If you just stop feeling it, you could start using it.
- 杀小孩的凶手 - 禽兽
- Child murderer! - Beast!
杀了他
Kill him!
佛莱迪
Freddy.
我们知道你要什么
We know what you want.
- 我要拥有一切 - 当然
- I want it all! - Of course you do.
- 那就敞开心胸 - 你就会永生不死
- Then open up. - And you shall be forever.
妈妈
Mommy.
另太担心 宝贝
Don't worry, baby.
妈妈必须吃药 因为她偷看爸爸特殊的作品
Mommy just had to take her medicine for snooping in Daddy's special work.
但你不会说出去 对不对
But you won't tell, will you?
我不会说出去
I won't tell.
但你说出去了 对不对
But you did tell, didn't you? Ha, ha.
现在该你吃药了
And now it's time to take your medicine.
你杀死我的母亲
You killed my mother!
她抓到他了
She's got him.
快点把她拉出来
Let's get her out of there.
我抓住你了
I've got you.
我抓住他了
I had him.
他在哪里
Where the hell is he?
- 或许这段旅程让他丧命 - 不
- Maybe the trip killed him. - No.
因为我还是看得见梦境中的东西
Because I'm still seeing things the way I did in my dream.
还没结束 我们走
It's not over. Let's go.
警察应该拿走这些东西
Cops were supposed to pick this stuff up.
幸好他们没拿走 我们需要用各种武器攻击他
Be glad they didn't. We're gonna have to hit him with everything we've got.
哇啊
Whoa!
瞧瞧这把刀
Check out this knife.
- 摆一边去 - 太小了
- Hey, put that away. - That's too small.
这应该可以
Guess so.
你确定它够大
You sure that's big enough?
- 你还是认为他会出现 - 对
- Still believe he's gonna show up, huh? - Yep.
崔西 过来
Come on, Tracy. Over here.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
- 你真实存在 - 这不是我的错
- You're real here. - It wasn't my fault.
并不是
It wasn't.
你也看见他们在我小时候 如何对待我
You saw what they did to me when I was a kid.
你看得很清楚
You saw.
我爱你
I loved you...
和你母亲
...and your mother.
我很努力当个好人
I tried so hard to be good.
我知道 爸爸
I know, Daddy.
但当他们把你从我身边夺走 这是不对的
But when they took you from me, it wasn't right.
我知道你相信我
Oh, I knew you'd believe me.
过来爸爸这里
Come to Daddy.
玛姬
Maggie.
我在这里
Over here.
我没事
I'm okay.
玛姬 小心
Maggie, watch out.
- 钥匙在哪里 - 我不知道
- Where's the key? - I don't know.
锁被卡住了
The lock's jammed.
我不需要手 就能杀死你妈那个贱女人
I didn't need a glove to kill your bitch of a mother...
现在我也不需要
...and I don't need one now.
快点 放手吧
Come on. Let go.
快点放手
Come on, let go.
- 不要 不要 - 下来
- No! No! - No! Get down.
让我示范给你看
I'll show you how.
像你示范给我母亲和卡洛斯看吗
Like you showed my mother and Carlos?
还有史宾瑟
And Spencer?
- 手套还给爸爸 小公主 - 你休想
- Give Daddy the glove back, princess. - Never.
还给我
Give it to me.
手套还给我
Give it to me. Give me that glove.
Give me the glove.
你做梦
In your dreams.
爸爸
Oh, Daddy.
我记得小时候我们都会手牵手
I remember when we used to hold hands together when I was a kid.
- 当时我也不喜欢 - 啊
- I didn't like it then either. - Aah!
我忘了当人类有多痛
I forgot how much it hurts to be human.
玛姬
Maggie.
搞什么
What?
快点
Come on.
你
Oh, you...
动手吧
Go ahead.
把它戴上
Put it on.
这是你的天性
It's in your blood.
很好 戴上吧
That's it, put it on.
感觉很棒吧
Feels good, doesn't it?
对 动手吧
Yeah. Come on.
让爸爸示范该如何使用
Let your daddy show you how to use it.
玛姬 玛姬
Maggie! Maggie!
父亲节快乐
Happy Father's Day.
加油
Come on. Yeah.
我们快点离开这里
Come on, let's hurry. Let's get out of here. Come on.
孩子们
Kids.
- 你还好吗 - 我没事
- You all right? - Yeah, I'm okay.
佛莱迪死了
Freddy's dead.